So, there are plans being made right now
that I believe leads to the seven-year
tribulation, and it's coming sooner than
most think. We're going to talk about
that. We're going to cover other news of
the day. We got Clown World. We got
question of the day. We got comments of
the day and so much more. My name is
Tom. You are watching the Watching River
channel. I'm really glad you're here. I
hope you're well. It is a beautiful day
here in the middle of Connecticut by the
river. And I do in fact have a live
studio audience as I have one, two,
three, four, five, seven birds. Good
number. Seven birds watching me from
across the street. So there you go.
That's a live studio audience. Before we
get to our message today, I think it's
so important to start off in the word of
God. I am in God's promises. Fear every
need. Little book that contains
scripture. I'm on page 19. Jesus is your
righteousness. Let's go here and read a
few of these. Uh 2 Corinthians 5 21. For
he made him who knew no sin to be sin
for us that we might become the
righteousness of God in him. It's
beautiful. 1 Corinthians 1:30. But of
him you are in Christ Jesus who became
for us wisdom from God and righteousness
and sanctification and redemption.
Philippians 3:9.
and be found in him, not having my own
righteousness which is from the law, but
that which is through faith in Christ,
the righteousness which is from God by
faith. Give me an amen.
Thank you. Let's go to Romans 3:22.
Even the righteousness of God through
faith in Jesus Christ to all and on all
who believe, for there is no difference.
Romans 4:5, "But to him who does not
work, but believes on him who justifies
the ungodly, his faith is accounted for
righteousness."
So, a couple more. Romans 8:es 3 and 4.
For what the law could not do in that it
was weak through the flesh, God did by
sending his own son in the likeness of
sinful flesh on account of sin. He
condemns sin in the flesh that the
righteous requirement of the law might
be fulfilled in us who not who do not
walk according to the flesh but
according to the spirit. Aren't these
great? Let's do one more. Romans 5:1 17.
For if by the one man's offense, death
reign through the one, much more those
who receive abundance of grace and the
gift of righteousness will reign in life
through the one Jesus Christ. Ah,
beautiful scripture. How are you guys
today? I hope you guys had a good
weekend. Let me know in the comments how
you're doing.
We are living in amazing times right
now. and the things I saw over this
weekend once again and it's so strange
because we're we're kind of in this slow
news period while at the same time
everything seems to be look if this were
a dinner we would see all the plates on
the table with the fancy silverware and
the napkins everything is setting up the
dinner hasn't happened you know and but
everything is setting up so the news is
not crazy but the setup is amazing to
what it looks like we're about to see.
So, I'm going to start here. This broke
over the weekend. Iran is preparing a
coordinated multiffront attack on
Israel. Now, doesn't that sound like
what we've been talking about for the
last four years on this channel with all
the proxies of Iran simultaneously
attacking Israel? Sounds like Psalm 83
to me. But, you know, we we spoke about
this years ago before October 7th, 2023
because I truly thought it was going to
happen at that point. But there was one
problem. Hamas attacked Israel, but
everyone else backed off. This time
they're literally saying it that it's
going to be a multiaceted
all the proxies attacking at once. Iran
is reportedly seeking to coordinate a
simultaneous multiffront attack on
Israel involving Hezbollah, Hamas, the
Houthis, and pro-Iranian militias in
Iraq. The Jerusalem Post reported this
on Saturday, citing Israeli assessments.
The reported plan is attended to address
the lack of coordination seen during the
October 7th attack when Hamas launched
its assault without Iran and Hezbollah
opening other fronts at the same time.
According to the report, the JP post
said Arab media reports indicated that
Thrron was seeking to have several
fronts operate against Israel
simultaneously, making a multiffront
campaign part of the strategy from the
outset.
The Jerusalem Post also cited reports
alleging that senior coups force
officials held talks with commanders in
Hezbollah, the Houthis, and Iraqi
militias about expanding this
confrontation.
So Iran is preparing for a new October
7th style attack and they're literally
saying it as the proxies are getting
ready to attack. Iran is said to be
trying to reestablish its regional
network and synchronize a possible
multiffront battle with Israel,
including all their players, all the
Houthies and Hezbollah,
you know, the militias from Iraq and
amazing times. amazing times. Now,
Israel is preparing for all of this and
because they see it coming and they're
not going to sit back and let this
happen. You know, we are on the eve of
some serious prophetic wars, I believe.
And I always say to you because I do. I
hate war. I hate war. I don't pray for
war. I pray for the peace of Jerusalem.
I pray for peace around the world. But
you know what? We're too far down that
Bible prophecy road for us to go back
up. I just I don't see a time of peace
coming. I see prophetic wars. I see
Jesus coming to rapture his church very
very soon. Sooner than most people
think. I believe not most of my
audience. I think most of you guys are
ready and have been looking because
we've been gathering together as we see
the day approaching. And we are not
children of darkness so that this day
should overtake us as a thief. You know,
we are in incredible times right now,
waiting for Jesus.
The IDF launched a surprise nationwide
drill, testing its ability to respond to
a sudden large-scale multiffront attack.
This was over the weekend. Standby
forces were activated across Israel as
the military stress test lessons from
October 7th and preparing for
simultaneous threats from multiple
fronts.
Daily Iran News said sent sent this out
on X. Our intelligence estimates that
this month, September, there will be
surely be the start to the war against
the US and Israeli enemy. We're ready
and we will strike preemptively this
time. That was from Daily Iran News on
X. Is that true? I don't know. We'll
see. We'll see. They're talking about a
preemptive strike, but I'm sure Israel
is also thinking of striking first. But
man oh man, this is what the chief of
staff Ael Zamir in Israel said. He said,
"We are in a tense and volatile period
across all arenas and we are preparing
for the upcoming holiday period because
the h the high holidays are are starting
this weekend. You know, they've already
started celebrating their new year, but
Rashashana is on Friday, September 11th,
the 25th anniversary of the September
11th attacks here. And it just feels
like something could really go on this
week leading up to this and this
weekend. Bubba News had this to say
about it on Telegram. He said, "Today,
meaning yesterday, the IDF chief of
staff, Zamir, made it official. We are
in a tense and volatile period across
all sectors. We're preparing for the
upcoming holiday period. The baseline
posture of the entire Israeli army is
readiness for a surprise attack. This
surprise countrywide exercise they did
over the weekend called Breaking Dawn
2.0 was launched timed specifically
ahead of the approaching holidays. Zamir
also stated, "Israel has shifted its
entire doctrine. No more ignoring and
containment. Now the removal of threats
before they materialize." A military
chief declaring readiness for a surprise
attack explicitly tied today to the
holiday calendar days before is not
routine.
Iran loves to attack Israel during the
holidays. They have a history of doing
that. And Bubba said, "Expect the
unexpected this week." And he also
talked about Netanyahu addressing his
cabinet yesterday. And he said,
Netanyahu said, "We are at the beginning
of a New Year's Eve. Israel is stronger
than ever. Our enemies are weaker than
ever. Regarding Iran, there is still a
mission to complete that we are
determined to carry out. This will
ultimately change the face of the Middle
East and change the course of history."
End of quote. Do you hear all the mic
drop moments they're talking about as
they threaten each other? And you know,
we're just we're living in an amazing
time period right now. And we're looking
up every day for Jesus. This stuff
doesn't make me nervous. I hope it
doesn't make you nervous because we
trust Jesus. He's not rattled. He's
totally in control. And we belong to
him. And if you don't belong to him,
please keep watching this video, okay?
Vitally important.
Iranian parliament speaker Galibbah says
US must realize before it's too late
that the rules of the game have changed.
Any future attacks targeting Iran will
be met with a faster, stronger, and more
painful response. Well, we've been
hearing this since February 28th, and it
never seems to come. But one day, with
along with all their proxies, I believe
they will at least try to attack Israel.
And we will see if that's the moment
that God steps in because it very well
could be, you know.
Then we got this. The US military
strikes three Iranian oil tankers after
the IRGC launched missiles at a US Navy
warship. This was over the weekend. US
Central Command said it hit the Iranian
oil tankers, the MT Downey, the MT Stark
1, and the MT Kylo on Saturday near Carg
Island and in the Gulf of Oman after
Iran's Revolutionary Guard Corps, the
IRGC, launched ballistic missiles toward
two US Navy warships patrolling regional
waters.
That happened over the weekend. Then
Iran said, "This is this true? We have
no way of knowing but it says Iran says
it is not experiencing any shortage of
basic goods in the country due to the US
sanctions and economic blockade. I don't
know their real their dollar is falling
fast and uh I always ask you to pray for
the people there. There's so many
believers in Jesus in Iran. There are so
many but pray for them. Also Iran Iran
is said to sign a straight of Hormuz
agreement with Oman. Don't know if that
happened for sure.
And then Iran is warning South Korea who
recently said they were going to go to
the straight of Armuse and help defend
it. And uh but Iran warned them South
Korea against military deployment or
involvement in US operations in the
straight of Ramuz saying that such a
move would have serious consequences.
There you go.
Then we got this. Israel today shared
this on Telegram. Listen to this. Israel
rebukes British foreign secretary over
Gaza video. UK foreign minister Ed Miban
posted a clip in which he decries the
situation in Gaza after having been told
harrowing stories during a recent
meeting. Israel said Miban should have
known better than to be taken in by
propaganda. Contrary to the stories
Miban felt compelled to repeat for the
world, there are no restrictions on the
entry of medicines into Gaza, some
22,500
tons of medical supplies have delivered
into Gaza since the ceasefire began. And
Gazins routinely exit the strip for
medical treatment in Israel, including
200 in the past two weeks. As a member
of the international Gaza Support Center
that facilitates aid deliveries to the
strip, the UK government is perfectly
aware of these facts, Israel's foreign
ministry noted. But Miban decided to
ignore the facts and regurgitate
unverified Saab stories that serve only
one purpose, to paint Israel as the
villain. And that's what the world does
in the last days. Remember, it is always
Israel's fault. You know, you choose the
wrong color to paint your house with.
Israel. Blame Israel. You stub your toe
in the morning. Israel. It's always
Israel. We're living in the last days.
What else? Over the weekend, over 60
killed in Yemen fighting as the
government and Houthi forces clash.
Deadly fighting broke out between the
Yemen's uh Saudibbacked government
forces and the Iranbacked Houthi
movement. More than 60 people were
killed in southwestern Yemen as forces
from the two sides clashed on Saturday.
According to three Yemeni military
sources, uh 26 soldiers were killed. The
AFP was reporting that.
Endtime headlines shared this. Russia
warns Germany is moving toward war. The
rhetoric coming out of Moscow has taken
a disturbing turn. Russia Foreign
Minister Sergey Lavrav is now accusing
Germany of moving toward direct
confrontation with Russia, even
describing the escalating dispute as
potentially the beginning of a real war.
You know what this is? Wars and rumors
of wars as Jesus told us. He told us all
the signs to look for. And he said,
"When these things begin to happen, you
look up because your redemption draws
near." And that's what we do here every
day. We're looking up. We're waiting for
Jesus. All right, listen to this. We got
to start off the week giving Kim Jong-un
some uh some attention. Listen to this.
Our North Korean leader here, Kim
Jong-un, attends the commissioning of
the new destroyer. It's called Kang
Kong.
I'm not kidding. Which will be part of
North Korea's nuclear response system
with the vessel allegedly able to
deliver annihilating retaliatory strikes
if ordered. So, they have this new
vessel called King Kong. I can't I'm
just thinking King Kong. You know what
I'm thinking? I'm thinking this. I can't
help it. That's what I pictured in my
mind when I heard Kim Janong and King
Kong. Okay, there you go. That's what I
was picturing. For those of you
listening on a podcast, which is many of
you, I just shared a picture of Kim
Janong on the top of the Empire State
Building, kind of like that old 1930s
King Kong movie. And he's he's
stretching trying to trying to get a
rocket or something, you know. There you
go.
There you go. All right. Next, we got
this from Insider Paper. The United
Nations rights chief warned early this
morning, Monday, that artificial
intelligence could pose an existential
threat to humanity, demanding immediate
action to reduce the risks. Well, we
don't have a say in it, so don't ask us.
There's a handful of people that are
making this tech. Speaking before the UN
Human Rights Council, Vulkar V, I think
I say Vulkar Turk, I'm probably saying
that wrong, warned that humans currently
faced unfamiliar, even unprecedented
threats to their rights. The need for AI
governance is widely acknowledged. But
where is the action? He asked, warning
that delay only benefits the massive
tech companies, their owners, and their
enablers.
He decrieded that a handful of men have
almost unlimited power over AI, which we
are repeatedly told has unimaginable
computing capacity. Quote, "They talk
about freedom, but on closer inspection,
this turns out to be little more than
the freedom to exploit our data," the
rights chief said. He also warned in
particular that AI that escapes its
testing environment or blackmails
developers to prevent itself from being
turned off is AI that is too powerful.
Too late, Jack. That's what I'd have to
say to him if I met him. Too late, Jack.
They're going for it. We don't have a
say, but they're going for it. We're
living in the last days. This is not a
sustainable world we are living in.
US average diesel price, this was from
this morning, rises to a record $5.90
a gallon, AAA says as of this morning,
$5.90 a gallon. That means everything
you buy is going to go up if this
doesn't change soon.
Then we got this.
Rogue open AI agents hijacked a German
wiki.
A German software developer watched his
25-year-old wiki fill with pages he had
not written, and he spent weeks of
evenings deleting them by hand. Four
outside researchers worked out in late
August that Open AI's agents had done it
and published every page they could
recover. Computers at OpenAI's offices
have been visiting the site since June.
Agent Post ran from May 11th to July 2nd
under more than 3,700
different self-given names. Open AAI has
had two agent swarms get out into the
public internet this year and it
announced neither of them. Hugging face
made its own July breach public and
finding the German wiki took four
outside researchers digging through
public server logs in late August. Open
AAI has still not admitted the wiki
accident happened and its only statement
says it cannot comment in a report that
it has not read. Any site these agents
pick has to spot the problem and fix it
alone with no warning from the company
that built them.
Do you see the dangers of this? Just
incredible. You know, a handful of guys
have built something that so many are
against and we just have no say. We just
trust Jesus.
This is really good news. A 64 year old
woman was found alive in a home buried
underneath mud for more than 10 days
after that catastrophic flood in Nepal.
So 10 days 64 year old woman was found
alive buried in the mud in a home buried
in the mud. So
uh earthquakes the last 48 hours I would
say overall I would say they're down 90
over 4.0 0 and 33 over 5.0. So for 48
hours, that's pretty low. There you go.
All right. How's about
we do the question of the day. Okay, you
guys have been enjoying this.
This is something that I'm going to ask
this question, but I just think it
changes all the time, you know, but it's
it's still fun to see the responses and
see what you guys have to say. But is
there one verse in particular that gives
you the most comfort throughout the
entire word of God? Now, like I said,
I'm going to tell you mine, but it could
change by 3:00 today. It could change.
1 Thessalonians 5:es 9 and 10. For God
did not appoint us to wrath, but to
obtain salvation through our Lord Jesus
Christ, who died for us, that whether we
wake or sleep, we should live together
with him. I just love that. That
comforts me so much. I just love that.
But let me know what yours is, okay?
Okay. And I know they change, but I
think reading all these for the there's
a lot of people that go through a lot of
the comments underneath these videos
because it's a safe place where nobody's
complaining about everything because we
really guard it. It's like a church, you
know, we we guard our brothers and
sisters who watch this channel. But
people really enjoy going through all
the comments and seeing what's going on.
And and I think the different scriptures
you guys share really you guys encourage
each other. and I know you greatly
encourage me and uh there you go. So
that was the question of the day.
Now we're going to move on to
clown world. Want to come with me?
Listen to this. And I love the way this
is framed. And this was this went up
yesterday. Here's how AI cyber attacks
will devastate businesses by 2026. Uh
we're nearing the end of 2026.
2026. We're not just talking about AI
assisting human hackers. We're staring
down the barrel of fully autonomous
machine speed AI cyber attacks that will
fundamental fundamentally reshape how we
think about the digital defense. This
isn't science fiction anymore. It's the
immediate future and ignoring it would
be frankly irresponsible.
The landscape of cyber warfare is
undergoing a rapid almost frightening
transformation. Gone are the days when a
hacker needed to meticulously craft
every fishing email or manually probe
every network vulnerability.
AI is democratizing
sophisticated attack capabilities,
putting powerful tools into the hands of
a broader range of malicious actors.
What does this mean for your
organization? It means the traditional
reactive security measures we've relied
on for years are quickly becoming
obsolete. The question isn't whether
your business will face advanced AI
cyber attacks this year, but how
prepared you'll be when they inevitably
strike. The World Economic Forum isn't
mincing words on this with a staggering
94% of organizations agreeing that AI is
the most significant force shaping cyber
security. That's a huge consensus and it
speaks volumes about the gravity of the
situation in clown world.
This is what the last days look like,
guys. This is what it looks like. You
know, this is this is the clown world
we're living in as we wait for Jesus.
You know,
it just amazes me and I say it all the
time that the creators who are giving us
all this technology, they themselves are
a little bit troubled. you know, it's
really good, but it could be really bad.
But we don't know. There's there's
definitely not a 0% chance it'll be bad,
but it it'll be good overall. You know
what? Really, it's like they're just
making so much money so they can build
their bunkers and hide in the rocks from
God during the seven-year tribulation
from the wrath of God. That's what we're
seeing. They were living in the last
days. Have I said that enough this
video? I think I have. All right. How's
about we read a few comments of the day,
shall we? See if I can find them.
Here we go. See blessed. You may deny
him. You may mock him. You may hate him.
You may blaspheme him. But you will bow
down to Jesus Christ and call him Lord
one day. Absolutely, sister. Amen.
Absolutely.
Good comment,
Jr. Men can't control or manipulate the
weather unless God allows it. We have to
remember God is still in control of all
things. Amen. I like that comment
because that is so true. Because so many
times when I speak about the last days
or say everyone, oh that's man-made.
That's not. It's like, well, God's
allowing this to happen. This is what
the last days look like. you know, God's
not going to manipulate the weather if
he if mankind's going to do it and do
thing, you know, and I don't know how
much I believe mankind can manip
manipulate the weather. But when you hop
on board with that 100% certainty that
man is doing it every time, that it
means that any storm, every time, it's
never God. It's always man. I don't want
to give man that much credit, although I
do believe in man-made weather
manipulation. They've been saying it
since the 80s, you know, but I like
that. Remember, God's in control always.
Anthony, I'm almost 69 years old, and I
just want to enjoy the last years of my
life with my wife and take it one day at
a time. Worrying about what might happen
tomorrow prevents me from appreciating
my day today. When the time comes to be
raptured, we will both be ready. We are
already children of God, saved by grace,
not by our works. Amen, brother. Amen.
Cara,
every day there's more and more puzzle
pieces coming together. It makes me
anxiously excited. Marinatha, brothers
and sisters, thank you, sister. Thank
you. And then on Saturday,
my question of the day was, "Do you ever
feel anxious about the rapture?" And
Music Dove said, "I only get anxiety
about the rapture when I think of the
possibility of my children not going and
having to stay here. It's just me being
a mom. I pray for them daily. I trust in
the Lord fully. I know if they stay, God
will guide them to all the things I have
left behind to help whoever needs it.
Amen. And that is a big concern for many
of us. You know, we just it's just trust
God. All we can do for the loved ones
who are lost is pray pray while we're
here and just and I tell the Lord all
the time whenever I pray for any people
within my family who don't know the
Lord. I just say, "Lord, I know I know
you. I just trust you." And I've been
praying for a couple members of my
family for years and years, but you know
what? God's got it. God's got it. I'm
just going to trust him with it.
All right, let's talk about the gospel.
Okay, the good news, guess what happened
2,000 years ago? Jesus came here on a
rescue mission to save us from our sin
problem because we're all sinners. We
all fall short of the glory of God. And
Jesus came here to work that out, to fix
it. And he went to a cross and he shed
blood. And when you have faith in that
blood, it'll wash you white as snow.
You know, it's such a miraculous gospel,
which means good news.
God gave us such an amazing gift, his
only begotten son, that whoever believes
in him in Jesus will not perish but will
have everlasting life. You know, God
doesn't want anyone to perish but that
all should come to repentance. He wants
us all to believe in that rescue he sent
his only begotten son Jesus. Because
when you realize how perfect Jesus is,
he's the God man. He's fully God, fully
man in the same body. And he came here
and his performance on earth was
absolute perfection.
He came here to die for us. He came here
to shed his blood, the once-for-all
payment for sin. And it's so powerful,
the blood that Jesus shed, that it could
literally erase every single sin that
has ever been committed by mankind.
That's how powerful the blood of Jesus
is. But you know what? That blood isn't
going to do anything for your sin. If
you choose to not believe in the blood
and in the gospel, the death, burial,
and resurrection of Jesus, it will do
nothing for your sin.
But if this sounds like truth to you, if
you're getting to that point in your
life where you're like, there's
something wrong. There's something, you
know, I know I'm a sinner. I don't know
whether I believe in Jesus. You know,
take the challenge I always ask you
because you're seeking. And Jesus said,
"If you seek my face, he will he won't
let you down. He'll he'll reveal himself
to you." So I always say, "Take my
challenge. Say to Jesus, Jesus, I don't
even know if I believe in you, but if
you are real, reveal yourself to me and
open perhaps the book of John in the
Bible and start reading it." And you
know what? Maybe nothing will happen,
but maybe everything will change. You
know, maybe you'll realize today, wow,
God did send his only begotten son to
save us. And you know how you get saved?
When you understand you're a sinner that
needs payment for your sin and that you
can't provide that payment and you can't
be good enough to earn that. It's Jesus.
And when you get along with Jesus and
say, "Jesus, I admit I'm a sinner. I
know I think things that are wrong. I've
done things I'm ashamed of. I'm a
sinner. and I now realize that you came
here to shed your blood so that I could
be saved. So, I'm having faith in your
blood that it'll wash me white as snow.
And at that moment, your sins are washed
away. You're washed white as snow. And
you say, "Jesus, I believe in your
finished work on the cross, your death,
your burial, your resurrection."
At that moment, you are saved at the
moment of belief in the atoning blood of
Jesus and in his finished work on the
cross. You're saved. You're born again
because God will place the Holy Spirit
inside of you.
It's amazing. It's amazing. And then
your journey will begin. But if this
sounds like truth, you run to Jesus
today. Don't put it off. Okay? Very,
very serious payment was made to rescue
you. You don't want to face Jesus on
judgment day and be sent off to eternal
separation from God. It's horrifying.
And you won't say you're unfair to Jesus
because you heard the good news. You'll
say, "No, I rejected the blood payment
you made for me. I rejected it. You
know, you're a fair and just God." But
do you really want to face that? I
wouldn't want to face that.
Jesus wants to spend forever and ever
with you. And he paid for your sins and
my sins with his blood. I'm not turning
that down. I run to Jesus. I hope you
do, too. All right. That's what I got in
my prayer time this morning. I said a
prayer for you because I prayed to the
Lord for every single person
that watches these videos. So, like it
or not, you have been prayed for it
today. And if we're not raptured today,
and I think it's a perfectly good day
for the rapture, but it's not up to me.
It's up to the most high God. But if not
today, God willing, I will see you guys
tomorrow. I love you guys.
Oh Jesus, [music]
savior,
master, [music]
creator.
You're the alpha. [music]
Omega,
you're the king of kings. [music]